netsbanking.com 2012-05-19

# Политика конфиденциальности

Privacy Policy

##### PERSONAL INFORMATION

For the operation of **NetsBanking** service and the reduction of fraud risks, NetsBanking must ask you to provide us with information about yourself. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use this information. We encourage you to acquaint yourself with this Privacy Policy. NetsBanking takes the safety of your personal information security very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the conditions of this Privacy Policy. We will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

However, as it is described in more detail below, there are limited circumstances in which some of your personal information will be disclosed to third parties under strict restrictions, therefore it is very important for you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all services that are placed in the NetsBanking system, whether the services are offered by NetsBanking or its subsidiaries on behalf of **NetsBanking**. 

Accepting this Privacy Policy when registering your account, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you object to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not register with us as Users. 

##### NOTIFICATION REGARDING CHANGES

This Privacy Policy may be revised over long time as new features are added to the **NetsBanking** service or as we incorporate suggestions from our investors. When something changes the Privacy Policy page will be updated with changes and published. Check out **NetsBanking.com** website from time to time for the updates on the latest version of our Privacy Policy.

 **NetsBanking** system also refers to the links to third party sites. These locations are identified by their own statements regardingPrivacy and **NetsBanking** is not responsible for their activities, including but not limited to their information practices. Investors presenting the information to third party sites should review the provision regarding the Privacy Policy of these sites prior to providing them with personal information. 

##### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

In order to open an account with **NetsBanking.com** you should indicate your name, e-mail address and your date of birth. This information is required for processing transactions, issuing a new password and, in case you lose your password—for protecting you and other **NetsBanking** investors from identifying information theft and getting in touch with you should the need to manage your account arise. For safety reasons we keep your personal information including the information regarding all your transactions through **NetsBanking.com** website, even after your account has been closed. We also save the Internet address (IP-address) of the computer or device used to access **NetsBanking** account in order to help detecting possible cases of unauthorized transactions. 

##### INFORMATION REGARDING NETSBANKING WEBSITE MOVEMENT

We also collect information regarding the pages on our website that you visit while on **Netsbanking.com** , what type of browser you use and how many times you visit our website. This information is used to understand the preferences of our investors and to manage the load on our services which helps us to improve our system and your experience of working with **NetsBanking.com**. We do not track the websites you visit before logging in or logging off **NetsBanking.com** website. 

##### OUR USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are small data files located on your computer that allow us to recognize you as the owner of **NetsBanking** account in case you return to **Netsbanking.com** website using the same computer and browser. We send a session cookie to your computer once you log in to your **NetsBanking** account, entering your ID and password. These files enable us to recognize you when you visit several pages on our website during one session. Once you log out or close your browser these session cookies expire and are no longer valid.   

##### CONNECTION

When you send us correspondence including through the use of e-mail, we keep this information in the records of your account. We will also retain correspondence from **NetsBanking** to you. We retain these records to assess and improve the services provided to Investors and to investigate potential fraud and violations of our Terms and Conditions. In addition to this, your phone calls to us and our phone calls to you will be monitored or recorded for quality, security and fraud detection purposes. 

##### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

 **NetsBanking** will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties. We exchange information with companies that help us process transactions, your inquiries and the protection of our Investors’ transactions from fraud. We disclose information that we believe in good faith should be used in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity or to conduct investigations of violations of our Terms and Conditions. 

##### ADDRESS AND INTERNET DATA

We use IP-addresses, browser types and access times to analyze trends, administer the **NetsBanking.com** website, improve the website and collect demographic data for aggregate use. 

##### UPDATING DATA

You can view the personal information you provided to us and make any necessary changes to this information or settings for your **NetsBanking** account at any time by logging into your account on **NetsBanking.com** and changing your preferences. If you close your **NetsBanking** account, we will mark your account in our database as closed, but we will keep the account information in our database. However, if you close your account, your personal information will not be used for further purposes or transferred to third parties, except for the cases necessary to promote the legislation. 

##### SAFETY

 **NetsBanking** aspires to process the information about Investors at a high security level. Your identification information is stored only in encrypted form. We restrict access to your personal information to employees who need to know this information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with regulatory requirements to guard your personal information. 

To access your account, you must enter your username and password each time. You can not share your **NetsBanking** password with anyone. If you suspect that your password has been compromised, you can change it at any time when you are logged into your **NetsBanking** account. When you transfer confidential personal account data to us on NetsBanking.com website, we require an Internet connection to be first set with SSL technology and that all data being transmitted must be encrypted.

Access to and use of password-protected secure sections of the **Netsbanking.com** website are limited to authorized users only.  
Unauthorized individuals attempting to access these sections of the **NetsBanking.com** website may be subject to investigation.  
The Investor is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any personal user names or passwords of the User.

The Investor bears full responsibility for all activities occurring under your User name and password, including the activities conducted by persons not authorized to use such passwords or User names.

The Investor agrees to immediately notify us about any unauthorized use of any of your User names or passwords. We reserve the right to require you to change your User name or password if we believe that it is no longer safe. **NetsBanking** will never ask you to send your password or other confidential information to us via e-mail although we may ask you to enter this type of information on **NetsBanking** website, which will always have a URL, starting with **http://www.NetsBanking.com.**

Any e-mail or other messages requesting your password or asking you to provide sensitive account information via e-mail or links to the website with a URL, which does not start with **http://www.NetsBanking.com** should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and must notify NetsBanking immediately.

If you have any questions about this **NetsBanking** Privacy Policy you can get in touch with us using the [contact page](http://www.netsbanking.com/support.php).

Update 10/03/2012
